[
  {
    "pregunta": "1",
    "respuesta": "2- 4 kg"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "2",
    "respuesta": "5"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "3",
    "respuesta": "30-40.000"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "4",
    "respuesta": "26"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "5",
    "respuesta": "250"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "6",
    "respuesta": ["Delante","Detrás","Encima"]
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "7",
    "respuesta": "96.400 km"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "8",
    "respuesta": "4"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "9",
    "respuesta": ["Sí","No"]
  }
  {
    "pregunta": "10",
    "respuesta": ["Carácter dominante que posee el 70% de la población","Genética"]
  }
]
